Ahmed Diaa

ahmeddiaa3465@gmail.com - www.ahmeddiaa.pro 01025812223 - 6th of October, Egypt

Objective

I am a highly skilled professional with extensive experience in the dynamic field of digital marketing. With a passion for staying ahead of industry trends and delivering exceptional results, with a deep understanding of search engine optimization (SEO), pay-per-click (PPC) advertising, social media marketing, content creation, email marketing, and web development.

Education

Diploma in Business Management

American Academy • 6th of October, Giza, Egypt

Bachelor in Business Administration

Canadian International College • 6th of October, Giza, Egypt

Oct 2017 - Feb 2018

Sep 2015 - Jan 2020

SKILLS

Personal Skills

- · Communication Skills
- Self-Confidence
- Self-Motivation
- Time Management
- Multitask
- · Attention to Details
- · Problem Solving
- Organized
- Team player

Technical Skills

- Adobe Indesign
- · Adobe illustrator
- · Microsoft Office Suite
- · Canva/Figma
- HTML/CSS/JS
- Data Analysis
- Content Creation

Work Experience

Web Developer Jan 2023 - Jun 2023

Freelancer • 6th of October, Egypt

I developed many websites for my clients in 6 months that attached in my portfolio.

Jan 2022 - Dec 2022 **SEO Specialist**

Freelancer • 6th of October, Egypt

I worked with multiple clients to improve their websites SEO by the following:

- · SEO Audit
- · Keyword Research
- On-Page SEO Optimization
- Off-Page SEO Optimization
- Technical SEO
- Local SEO

Office Assistant Jan 2021 - Nov 2021

Egyptian Military • Cairo, Egypt

- Determine and establish office procedures and routines
- Schedule and confirm appointments
- Answer electronic enquiries
- Compile data, statistics and other information
- Set up and maintain manual and computerized information filing systems
- Type and proofread correspondence, forms and other documents

Jun 2018 - Jul 2018 **Trainee**

QNB Bank • Cairo, Egypt

- Arrange and co-ordinate seminars, conferences, etc.
- · Determine and establish office procedures and routines
- Schedule and confirm appointments
- Answer telephone and relay telephone calls and messages
- Answer electronic enquiries
- Compile data, statistics and other information
- Set up and maintain manual and computerized information filing systems
- Type and proofread correspondence, forms and other documents

Trainee Aug 2017 - Aug 2017

QNB Bank • Cairo, Egypt

- Determine and establish office procedures and routines
- Schedule and confirm appointments
- Answer telephone and relay telephone calls and messages
- Answer electronic enquiries
- Compile data, statistics and other information
- Set up and maintain manual and computerized information filing systems
- Type and proofread correspondence, forms and other documents

Certifications

Adobe Indesign Certificate	2023
Adobe illustrator Certificate	2023
Advanced SEO Certificate	2023
Bootstrap 5 Certificate	2023
Content Marketing Certificate	2023
Digital Marketing Certificate	2023
Email Marketing Certificate	2023
Google Ads Certificate	2023
Google Analytics Certificate	2023
HTML/CSS/JS Certificate	2023
Node JS Certificate	2023
React JS Certificate	2023
Social Media Marketing Certificate	2023
Small Business Certificate	2023
Social Media Marketing Certificate	2023